<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
		<xpath>Defs/StorytellerDef[@Name="BaseStoryteller"]/comps/li[@Class="StorytellerCompProperties_ImportantQuest"]</xpath>
		<value>
			<li Class="VanillaGravshipExpanded.StorytellerCompProperties_ImportantQuestAfterResearch">
				<fireAfterDaysPassed>30</fireAfterDaysPassed>
				<research>Electricity</research>
				<questIncident MayRequire="Ludeon.RimWorld.Odyssey">GiveQuest_MechanoidSignal</questIncident>
				<questDef MayRequire="Ludeon.RimWorld.Odyssey">MechanoidSignal</questDef>
				<allowedTargetTags>
					<li>Map_PlayerHome</li>
				</allowedTargetTags>
				<enableIfAnyModActive>
					<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Odyssey</li>
				</enableIfAnyModActive>
			</li>
		</value>
	</Operation>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
		<xpath>Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="MechanoidSignal"]/questNameRules/rulesStrings/li</xpath>
		<value>
			<li>questName->runaway gravjumper</li>
		</value>
	</Operation>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
		<xpath>Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="MechanoidSignal"]/questDescriptionRules/rulesStrings</xpath>
		<value>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>questDescription-> You've been contacted by the Trading Guild with an urgent offer. One of their gravships carrying classified and dangerous cargo has gone rogue. The crew is presumed dead, and the ship is now on a collision course with one of their orbital platforms. It is also closely followed by a mechanoid swarm.\n\nTo avoid further catastrophe, they propose to redirect the ship to crash near your location. In return, they grant you the salvage rights. The vessel will be heavily damaged, but its gravjumper engine should remain intact.\n\nBe warned: as soon as it crashes, the pursuing mechanoids will descend on your position.\n\nGravships are rare and powerful vessels, built to traverse planetary surfaces and breach low orbit without rockets. Owning even a damaged one could change the course of your colony’s future.</li>
				<li>gravEngineSpawnedLetterLabel->wrecked gravjumper engine</li>
				<li>gravEngineSpawnedLetterText->The damaged Trading Guild vessel has crashlanded nearby.\n\nAmidst the wreckage, you spot a functional gravjumper engine: a compact gravity manipulation core used to lift ships from planetary surfaces into orbit. The ship seems badly damaged, and substantial repair will be required.\n\n\n\nInspect the engine to make use of it and unlock the basic gravtech research project.</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</value>
	</Operation>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
		<xpath>Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="MechanoidSignal"]/root</xpath>
		<value>
			<root Class="VanillaGravshipExpanded.QuestNode_Root_MechanoidSignal_Expanded"/>
		</value>
	</Operation>
</Patch>
