<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <VGE_TargetingTerminalCanOnlyLinkWithGravshipArtillery>Targeting terminal can only link with gravship artillery.</VGE_TargetingTerminalCanOnlyLinkWithGravshipArtillery>
    <VGE_NeedsLinkedTargetingTerminal>Needs a linked targeting terminal.</VGE_NeedsLinkedTargetingTerminal>
    <VGE_LinkWithTerminal>Link with a terminal</VGE_LinkWithTerminal>
    <VGE_LinkWithTerminalDesc>Select a targeting terminal to link with. A targeting terminal is required to operate gravship artillery.</VGE_LinkWithTerminalDesc>
    <VGE_UnlinkWithTerminal>Unlink with a terminal</VGE_UnlinkWithTerminal>
    <VGE_UnlinkWithTerminalDesc>Break the current link to a targeting terminal, allowing you to link with a different one.</VGE_UnlinkWithTerminalDesc>
    <VGE_SelectLinkedTerminal>Select linked terminal</VGE_SelectLinkedTerminal>
    <VGE_SelectLinkedTerminalDesc>Show the linked targeting terminal.</VGE_SelectLinkedTerminalDesc>
    <VGE_SetWorldTarget>Set world target</VGE_SetWorldTarget>
    <VGE_SetWorldTargetDesc>Set the target on the world map for the gravship artillery to fire at. Shots fired over the world map are less accurate. Can only fire at revealed locations.</VGE_SetWorldTargetDesc>
    <VGE_NeedsMannedTargetingTerminal>Needs a manned targeting terminal.</VGE_NeedsMannedTargetingTerminal>
    <VGE_LinkWithTurret>Link with a turret</VGE_LinkWithTurret>
    <VGE_LinkWithTurretDesc>Select a turret to link with. This targeting terminal will be used to operate that turret.</VGE_LinkWithTurretDesc>
    <VGE_UnlinkWithTurret>Unlink turret</VGE_UnlinkWithTurret>
    <VGE_UnlinkWithTurretDesc>Break the current link to a turret, allowing you to link with a different turret.</VGE_UnlinkWithTurretDesc>
    <VGE_SelectLinkedTurret>Select linked turret</VGE_SelectLinkedTurret>
    <VGE_SelectLinkedTurretDesc>Show the linked turret.</VGE_SelectLinkedTurretDesc>
    <VGE_GravshipArtilleryNeedsVisibleMap>Gravship artillery needs to target a visible, explored map.</VGE_GravshipArtilleryNeedsVisibleMap>

    <VGE_ConfirmCrashLanding>Landing on this location will be considered a crash. Any highlighted structures underneath the gravship will damage any structures on the gravship in corresponding locations.\n\nThe substructure may also become damaged and will need replacing before the next launch.\n\nSome indestructible objects underneath may completely destroy the substructure and any objects on it.\n\nConsider picking a different landing zone.</VGE_ConfirmCrashLanding>
    <VGE_CrashLandingWarning>Landing on this location will be considered a crash and will damage the gravship.</VGE_CrashLandingWarning>

    <VGE_SoildIceAsteroid>Solid ice with traces of {RESOURCE_label}</VGE_SoildIceAsteroid>
	
	<VGE_Maintenance>Part maintenance: {0}</VGE_Maintenance>
	<VGE_Maintain>Maintain part</VGE_Maintain>
	<VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance>Gravship maintenance low</VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance>
	<VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>Some gravship components have low maintenance. This can result in negative launch outcomes and eventual break downs. Consider assigning a colonist to maintain them. Gravship components with low maintenance:\n\n {0}</VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>

    <!-- Mod options -->

    <VGE_OrbitObjectsMultiplier>Orbital objects multiplier</VGE_OrbitObjectsMultiplier>
    <VGE_OrbitObjectsMultiplierDesc>By default the game will try to keep 3,8,12 or 20 locations in orbit (depending on globe coverage of the planet). With this slider you can apply a multiplier to this number, making your planet orbits super sparse or very cluttered!</VGE_OrbitObjectsMultiplierDesc>
    <VGE_Reset>Reset</VGE_Reset>
    <VGE_HeatsinkHeatStored>{0} / {1} heat units</VGE_HeatsinkHeatStored>
    <VGE_AbsorbGravheat>Absorb gravheat</VGE_AbsorbGravheat>
    <VGE_AbsorbGravheatDesc>Flush any remaining structural heat from the grav engine onto this gravheat absorber, allowing for an immediate gravship launch. Gravheat absorber will enter a long cooldown period during which it can't absorb any more heat.</VGE_AbsorbGravheatDesc>
    <VGE_NoGravEngine>No grav engine found</VGE_NoGravEngine>
    <VGE_NoCooldownToAbsorb>No cooldown to absorb</VGE_NoCooldownToAbsorb>
    <VGE_GravheatAbsorberCoolingDown>Gravheat absorber is cooling down. Available in: {0}</VGE_GravheatAbsorberCoolingDown>
    <VGE_LaunchHeatsinkCooldownInfo>The heatsinks will reduce the launch cooldown time by {0}.</VGE_LaunchHeatsinkCooldownInfo>
    <VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructure>Remove substructure</VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructure>
    <VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructureDesc>Remove substructure from the gravship.</VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructureDesc>
</LanguageData>